Romain Day

IT STUDENT IN MOBILE
AND WEB DEVELOPMENT

CONTACT DETAILS

+33 6 49 65 65 19 romain.day.ludovic@gmail.com

24 rue du Général Hulot 54000 NANCY FRANCE

SKILLS

- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- Javascript
- Java
- PHP 7
- VueJS
- Bootstrap 4
- AngularJS

MASTERED TOOLS

- MySQL
- Win'design
- Git
- Docker
- Netbeans
- Visual Studio
- Windows 10
- Linux Ubuntu

OTHER INTERESTS

- Japanese Culture
- Video Games
- Photography

PROFILE

Currently in a vocational Bachelor's degree specialized in Mobile and Web Development, I am looking for an internship from May to July 2020. Before my Bachelor, I attended a 2-year technical degree in Software Solutions and Trades Applications. I work very well in team environment, I am self-taught person who loves challenges. At the moment, I am working on a school project in order to create a new social network.

WORK EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPMENT INTERN

Résidence Saint-Martial | Limoges, FRANCE | Jan 2019 - Feb 2019 | Skill development : CSS3, HTML5, PHP7, PHPMailer, Google Calendar API Mission : Develop a website and a web application promoting the intergenerational aspect of the residence.

DEPARTMENT EMPLOYEE

CORA (supermarket chain) | Limoges, FRANCE | July 2018 - Aug 2018 Mission: Manage the stock, install and label the items in the stationery department.

WEB DEVELOPMENT INTERN

CHU (university hospital) | Limoges, FRANCE | May 2018 - June 2018 | Skill development : CSS3, HTML5, PHP5, Connexion ODBC | Mission : Develop a web application for the Metrology department of the Limoges University Hospital.

DRIVE EMPLOYEE

Leclerc (supermarket chain) | Brive-la-Gaillarde, FRANCE | July 2017 - Aug 2017 Mission: Prepare customer shopping and place orders.

EDUCATION

VOCATIONAL BACHELOR

Specialized in Mobile and Web Development
Nancy University of Technology | Nancy, FRANCE | 2019 - 2020

TECHNICAL DEGREE

Specialized in Software Solutions and Trades Application Lycée Suzanne Valadon | Limoges, FRANCE | 2017 - 2019

FRENCH BACCALAUREATE

Specialized in Computer Sciences

Lycée Georges Cabanis | Brive-la-Gaillarde, FRANCE | 2017 - 2019